var wareHouse = [
    {
        question: "What's the less-than-or-equal-to symbol in programing?",
        selection: ["<", ">", "<=", ">="],
        answer: "<=",
    },
    {
        question: "What makes a string??",
        selection: ["text", "numbers", "symbols", "formulas"],
        answer: "text",
    },
    {
        question: "From which number does the amount of elements in an array begin??",
        selection: ["0", "1", "-1", "-0"],
        answer: "0",
    },
    {
        question: "How many possible values does a boolean have??",
        selection: ["0","2", "10", "infinite"],
        answer: "2",
    },
    {
        question: "This means it's equal in form and value:",
        selection: ["=", "==", "===", "!=="],
        answer: "===",
    },
    {
        question: "Who invented the internet??",
        selection: ["AlGore", "Albert Einstein", "Antonio Meucci", "Vinton Cerf and Bob Kahn"],
        answer: "Vinton Cerf and Bob Kahn",
    },
    {
        question: "Is there a difference between Java and JavaScript",
        selection: ["Yes.", "nah, same thing", "idk, is there?", "p e r h a p s"],
        answer: "Yes.",
    },
    {
        question: "What does CSS mean?",
        selection: ["Confidential Secret Society", "Counting Style Sheets", "Cascading Style Sheets", "Camp Sweet Summer"],
        answer: "Cascading Style Sheets",
    },
    {
        question: "What's my favourite color?",
        selection: ["White", "Red", "Green", "Black"],
        answer: "Red",
    },
    {
        question: "What does <hr> in HTML do?",
        selection: ["Thematic break", "Tax break", "Gives you the time", "Measure in hours"],
        answer: "Thematic break",
    },
];